http://www.kindermark.com/pages/privacy

×
Welcome!
Sign up for our newsletter to hear about special offers and new products!
We accept purchase orders. Call for details.
FREE SHIPPING* for Contiguous U.S.  Freight Charges may apply. Click HERE for details.
Shopping Cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Continue Shopping
My Account
Welcome to Kindermark Kids!
Privacy Policy
Kindermarkkids.com respects the privacy of its customers and product users and is committed to maintaining the privacy and confidentiality of the information that is collected from customers during registration and the continuing use of the Website.  The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to explain how Kindermarkkids.com collects, retains and uses personal information that may be collected during your use of the Website. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn about how we manage your personal information, including what information is gathered, why it is gathered, to whom Kindermarkkids.com discloses such personal information, and how your personal information is safeguarded by Kindermarkkids.com.
Why We Collect Personal Information
Collecting personal information is necessary to process purchase orders and communicate with customers.  Additionally, Kindermarkkids.com strives to provide superior service to its customers.  Collecting certain personal information helps Kindermarkkids.com achieve this goal by providing you with more convenient access to the Website and by ensuring that Kindermarkkids.com meets its internal quality standards.
Collection And Use Of Personal Information
We collect information from you at several different points on the Website and may maintain this information in our customer database.  When you register on the Website, you may be required to provide personal information, such as your name, address, phone number and email address. If you purchase any products or services on the Website, you will be required to provide certain financial information, such as credit card number and expiration date.  We use the information that we collect from you to enable billing, to fulfill orders, and to provide you with information about programs, special offers, and other products and services based on your preferences.  We also use this information to improve the Website, for development of new programs, products and services, and for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes.
The Website may use internet protocol (“IP”) addresses to analyze trends, administer the Website, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  Other information collected and presented during the use of the Website may include last log-in date, prior order details including product numbers, quantities and prices, discounts applied, favorite products, as well as that information further set forth below under Website Visit Tracking Technologies.
Website Visit Tracking Technologies
As is standard practice on many corporate websites, the Website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help understand which parts of the Website are the most popular and the preferences of Kindermarkkids.com users, as well as to facilitate navigation throughout the Website.  We may also use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on the Website, to improve its functionality and usability, as well as to improve the effectiveness of Kindermarkkids.com’s communications with its customers.  We may also use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience to you during your interactions with the Website.
A cookie is a unique alphanumeric identifier that websites use to help identify the number of unique visitors to a website, whether or not those visitors are repeat visitors, and the source of the visits.  Cookies cannot be executed as code or used to deliver a virus and thus pose no threat to you.  Servers and websites other than the one placing the cookie on your hard drive generally cannot read the cookie, and no personal information can be gathered by other servers from the cookie.  If you prefer not to enable cookies or to disable them, you may do so through your web browser’s security settings.  Please note that certain features of the Website may not be available once cookies have been disabled.
Like most websites, the Website may gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information may include IP addresses, browser type, operating system, internet service provider (“ISP”), referring/exit pages, date/time stamp of access, and clickstream data.  When you visit the Website, the server automatically logs your IP address, the time and duration of your visit, and the time and duration spent on the pages of the Website which you view.  If you arrive at the Website by clicking a paid advertisement or a link in an email, then the server will capture information that tracks your visit from that link.  If you arrive at the Website by clicking on a non-paid source, such as a search engine result or link on another website, the server may capture information that tracks your visit from that source, to the extent available.  We may use this information to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to track users’ movements around the Website and to gather demographic information about the Website's users as a whole.  Kindermarkkids.com may use the information collected to market directly to you with your consent.
In some of Kindermarkkids.com’s email messages we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Website.  When you click one of these URLs, it passes information through our web server before arriving at the destination web page.  Kindermarkkids.com tracks this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.  If you prefer not to be tracked, simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the emails sent.
Kindermarkkids.com may also use pixel tags, which are tiny invisible graphic images, to tell us what parts of our Website customers have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our Website.  Pixel tags may be used as part of Kindermarkkids.com’s use of third-party website statistics trackers and analyzers which Kindermarkkids.com employs to track and analyze the data collected from the Website.  Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read.  They also tell us whether emails have been opened to assure that Kindermarkkids.com is only sending messages that are of interest to our customers.  We store all of this information in a secure database on our web server.
When We Disclose Information
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information.  This does not include trusted third-parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.  However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Children
We do not knowingly collect any personal information from users under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly market to such users.  Nevertheless, if we become aware that a user under the age of 13 is attempting to register on the Website or order any products or services on the Website, we will ask that user to provide the email address of his or her parent or guardian.  We will then send that parent or guardian an email from us alerting them to the child’s activities.  We will not knowingly permit that child to continue such activities until we receive the appropriate consent of his or her parent or guardian.
How We Protect Your Personal Information
Kindermarkkids.com takes administrative, technical, and physical measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.  The Website uses SSL encryption when processing order information during checkout in the online store and collecting and storing any personal and order information.  You can also help Kindermarkkids.com by taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet.  Be sure to select a password that includes a combination of upper and lowercase letters and numbers which is difficult to guess and do not distribute your password or store it in an unsecure manner.  While on a secure page, such as our ordering form, a lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Google Chrome, Firefox and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just “surfing.”
Please be advised, however, that although we have endeavored to create a secure and reliable site for you, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from the Website cannot be guaranteed.  We urge you to exercise caution when conveying personal information over the Internet.  When disclosing any personal information, you should remain mindful of the fact that it is potentially accessible to the public and, consequently, may be collected and used by others without your consent.  You should therefore consider carefully if you want to submit sensitive information that you would not want disclosed to the public.  You should also recognize that your use of the Internet and the Website is solely at your own risk.  You agree that we have no responsibility or liability for the security of personal information transmitted via the Website or via the Internet in general.
Links
Kindermarkkids.com may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information.  The privacy practices of those sites may differ from Kindermarkkids.com’s practices and are not controlled by Kindermarkkids.com nor covered by this Privacy Policy.  Kindermarkkids.com does not make any representations about third-party websites.  Kindermarkkids.com encourages you to review the privacy policy of any third-party site before submitting any personal data.  Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
CAN-SPAM Compliance
We have taken steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 and do not send out misleading information.
Your Consent
By using the Website you consent to our collection and use of your Personal Information, Use Information and all other information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Privacy Contact
We welcome your questions and comments regarding this Privacy Policy and the use of personal information. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or about our information-collection practices, please contact us at CustomerService@Kindermarkkids.com.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Kindermarkkids.com reserves the right to amend the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, without notice to you.  If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.
This Privacy Policy was last modified on August 1, 2016
Menu
Home
Search
Blog
About Us
Payment Methods
Shipping
Return Policy
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Current Shipping Times for Sinks
Newsletter Sign Up
Sign up for our newsletter and be the first to know about
new products, coupons and special promotions.
Our Promise
We take pride in the quality of our products and the quality of our customer service. We stand behind what we sell and will do everything possible to insure total customer satisfaction.
© 2020 Kindermark Kids
|
FurnitureDecorToys
